I want to see what
virtual reality is like.
I wonder when I first thought that.
I used to hate virtual reality
games with a vengeance,
and I blamed them for stealing
my brother away from me.
but later on i got
curious i didn't know why
my brother loved them
so much so i figured.
maybe i should see why for myself.
i didn't know what to
expect at first but after a
while i was surprised by
how much i loved alfheim.
online it was amazing
flying through the sky
on my very own wings to
fly as far as i wanted.
as high as i wanted as fast as i wanted
i'd give anything and everything for that.
i think i get it now i can see why
my brother loves the virtual world.
If I'm here, I won't be
able to see the future.
I won't be able to see the sun again.
I'm going to cry.
If this is my dream, F
Hold it, Lefa! Huh!?
I thought I told you not to call me
that at school, Nagata. Didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
Sorry, Suguha. Idiot!
I'm sorry, I meant Kirigaya!
What do you want?
Wait, why are you even here?
You got a release from taking
the high school entrance exams.
They're not making you
come anyway, are they?
Sugu!
Kirigaya!
I need to talk to you, so
I've been waiting all morning.
Wait, you're not here
for the exams, are you?
No.
The advisor for the kendo club
asked me to come in, that's all.
Well, what's up?
It's Sigurd and the others.
They all wanted to go
hunting again this afternoon.
Sorry.
I won't be going out with
those guys for a while.
Wait, what? Why not?
I've got plans to head
over to Arun, that's why.
But isn't Arun at the
base of the world tree?
Wait a second! You... are you...
you're not going with that spriggan!
Yeah.
Well, sort of.
I promised I'd show him how to get there.
But have you thought about
what you're doing, Lee?
Kitty Gaia, it's just so far away,
and you guys will be sleeping
together, and they'll...
Don't get any weird
ideas about it, you jerk!
Look, I've made up my
mind, and that's that.
Say hey to Sigurd and the others for me.
See you later.
All I'm doing is showing him the way.
That's all I'm doing.
Link, start!
Hey there, been waiting long?
Not at all, I just walked in.
Actually, I was out shopping for gear.
Oh, that's right.
I should update my equipment, too.
I don't think this is going to be enough.
Okay.
I know a good weapon shop in town.
But do you have enough money?
Because they're not cheap.
Okay, money.
Wait, this thing called
Yule, is that money?
Uh-huh.
Hey, Yui, wake up. We're heading out now.
Okay.
Why'd we come here?
Well, when flying long distances, it's
better if you start from a higher altitude.
That's what the tower's here for.
Oh, that makes sense.
You're kidding me!
Come on, let's go!
I want to get past the forest before dark.
This way, Slowpoke!
Leafa!
Oh, uh, hello, Sigurd.
What's this I hear about
you leaving the party?
Is that true?
Well, yeah, it is.
Do you have any idea how much that's
going to upset the other members?
You said it wouldn't be a problem if
I joined only when I had the time.
You also said I could
quit whenever I wanted to.
Yes, I know what I said, but you've
been with us for a while now.
Everyone knows you.
If you leave us, it's going to
damage the reputation of the party.
Party members are not items.
What did you say?
Party members aren't items, so don't
expect them to be on call for you.
They're not your armor.
They're not your sword.
They're not your equipment.
You son of a...
I bet that big mouth of yours got
you thrown out of your own territory.
Let's see what you got, you
piece of spriggin' trash.
Okay, that's it. Enough.
Kirito's my new partner,
so leave him alone. What?
Leafa, you're abandoning us
to be a renegade like him?
Yes, I am.
And I'm not coming back ever.
I don't give a damn about you
buzzing around my party members.
But if you think you can steal
them, then that's another story.
If you're stupid enough to waltz
into another race's territory,
then it's your own damn fault
if you get killed, Spriggan!
This isn't the time or place, Sigurd.
If we gank this guy in front of all
these people, we're gonna look bad.
Once you cross our border, you
better run and hide, Leafa.
I never expected you to
betray me like this! Never.
But you'll regret it soon enough!
I'm really sorry you got
dragged into all that drama.
It's cool.
I'm worried about you, though.
Are you sure about this?
Hey, don't!
Wow.
This is an amazing view.
The sky's so close, it's like
I can reach out and touch it.
I know, right?
Whenever I look up at that sky,
everything else feels so small.
The timing couldn't have been any better.
I've been thinking about
leaving here for a while now.
Okay, but I feel like it's sort of my fault
you left on bad terms with those guys.
Yeah, well, I don't think it
could have happened any other way.
What do you mean by renegade?
A renegade's a player who
abandons their territory.
If you get branded as one,
everyone's going to look down on you.
And you're cool with that?
Yeah.
I don't really care.
But I don't understand why everyone's so
quick to tie each other down like that.
I mean, what's the point
in having wings, you know?
You humans are so complicated.
Honestly, your psychology is confusing.
Why do you act so horribly to each other
when all you want is companionship?
What do you mean?
If it were me, I'd do that.
It's simple, straightforward,
and efficient.
And, uh, that's an amazing AI.
Do all private pixies act
like that, or just yours?
No, just mine, but she's a weirdo.
I guess you would know, huh?
All we want is companionship.
Lipia!
Hey, Recon.
How could you do this?
You could have at least said
something before you left.
Oh, sorry, I guess I forgot.
Aw.
Why'd you quit the party
all of a sudden like that?
Well, I didn't really
think too hard about it.
I just did it.
What are you going to do, though?
As if, Leafa!
It doesn't matter where you go.
My sword belongs to you and you alone.
I don't need it, but thanks.
Oh.
What I meant by that was,
I'm going to go with you.
Wherever.
That is, I'd like to go, but there's
something that's been bugging me.
What is it?
I can't really prove anything yet,
but there's a few things I
want to look into some more,
so I'm going to stay in
Sigurd's party a little longer.
Hey, Kirito?
She has a habit of getting
herself in trouble.
I'd appreciate it if
you'd keep an eye on her.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever you say.
And just to make sure we're
absolutely clear, Lipa is my...
We'll be in the neutral zone for a while.
Message me if you need anything.
Let me get this straight.
In real life, he's your friend?
Yeah, something like that.
Okay, what's that weird
noise supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Just a little jealous is all.
Now that person's
feelings I can understand.
He must like you a lot.
Wouldn't you say, Lipa?
Do you feel the same way about him?
Uh, I don't know, jeez!
Hurry up, you guys!
Let's try to make it all the way
to the lake without stopping!
Okay!
Unbelievable you can be so stubborn
seriously no matter what I do I can't
hurt you it's not like that body's
real why can't you just loosen up and
enjoy yourself a little I don't
expect you to understand but to me it
doesn't matter if my body's real or
virtual you may not think that way but
I do are you afraid you're going to
be corrupted somehow because if that's
the case you definitely need to take
things a little less seriously while
you're here well I'm not planning on
staying in this cage forever you'll
see he'll come and save me really who
will that hero boyfriend of yours?
Goes by the name of Kirito.
Please.
You think I didn't know?
His real name's Kirigaya.
I met him the other
day, in the real world.
I couldn't believe that weak little boy
was the same one who beat Sword Art Online.
It took me a second to collect myself.
By the way, where do you think I met him?
In your hospital room.
As you were lying there, I told
him I'd be marrying you next week.
My God, you should have seen his face.
It was like all the
color drained out of it.
I could barely keep myself from laughing.
Do you want to know what I think?
I'll bet you anything that brat won't have
the guts to put on the
nerve gear ever again.
That reminds me.
I promised him I was going to
send along a wedding invitation.
I'm pretty sure he'll come.
He's going to want to see
you in your wedding dress.
I know. I'm generous.
The least I can do is leave
the little hero a few crumbs.
Well, I have to get going now, Titania.
I hope you don't miss me too much.
He's alive.
Kirito's alive.
Hm-hm.
8-1-1-3-2-3-2-9.
Nice job.
Thanks for the awesome backup.
Our wings aren't going
to last much longer.
I think we should land
down there for a bit.
Okay.
Hey, you getting tired
yet? Nope. I'm good to go.
Okay, Mr. Tough Guy.
I hate to break it to you, but flying's
out for both of us for a little while.
Huh? How come?
You see that mountain way over there?
It's above the altitude
limit, so we can't fly over.
The only way anyone can pass
it is to go through the caves.
It's the toughest part of the trip
between Sylph territory and Arun.
Or so I've heard.
I've never even been this far myself.
Guess we walk.
These caves, are they long? Pretty long.
There's a mining town about halfway.
It's neutral territory,
so we can rest there.
That reminds me.
Are you good for time, or
do you have to get back?
It's seven at night in the real world.
Yeah, I can keep going for a while.
Cool.
I can too, so let's keep going.
But since we're here,
we should rotate out.
Wait, rotate? Yeah.
We take turns logging out and
resting while the other keeps watch.
You can't log out when you're
in the field, remember?
So we have to take turns logging out.
The person who stays behind
guards the other's avatar.
Okay, sounds like a plan.
Ladies first.
Okay, don't mind if I do.
See you in about 20 minutes.
Hey, Kazuto, what do you
want to do for dinner?
I wonder if he's asleep.
I can't wait to get back there.
Kirito.
It's not that I'm in love
with him or anything,
or that I've got someone
to go on adventures with.
No.
I'm just excited I get to
go places in a new world.
Hey, I'm back!
Did you see any monsters?
No, I didn't.
It's been pretty quiet this whole time.
What are you eating?
I bought a bunch at a shop
before we left Sylvain.
I don't know what they're called, but
an NPC said you can only get them there.
I've never seen them before.
Sorry to leave you like
this, but it is my turn.
Keep me safe, okay?
Get out of here before I hurt you!
No way!
You can move when your
master's logged out?
Well, of course I can move!
You know, I'm my own person!
And for your information, he's
not my master, he's my daddy!
Yeah, about that.
I was gonna ask you before,
why do you call him your daddy?
Did he, you know, um, set
you that way or something?
He didn't do anything to my settings.
He saved me.
He told me I was his daughter.
That makes him my daddy.
You see how that works?
Yeah, I guess.
Do you, you know, like him?
I'm sorry.
I don't understand what you mean by like.
Are you serious?
It means you want to be
with him all the time.
And when you're together, you
get excited about being near him.
Or something like that.
What's wrong, Leafa? Nothing!
It's nothing! What's nothing?
What's going on?
What is it?
Did something happen?
Welcome back, Daddy.
Leafa was just explaining to me
what it means when someone said...
No!
I said it's nothing!
It's nothing!
You weren't there for very long.
I hope you got something to eat.
Yeah.
My family left something
for me, so I'm good.
Sweet. Come on, then. Let's get going.
Okay. All right. Lead the way.
Is something wrong? I don't know.
It sort of felt like
someone was watching us.
Hey, Yui.
There any players nearby?
No, I'm not sensing any other players.
Hmm, it's possible someone
put a tracer on us.
What the heck's a tracer?
A kind of tracking magic.
It looks like a small animal or an insect.
It tells the caster a target's position.
Can you dispel it?
Sure, if you can find it.
The thing is, if the
caster's magic skill is high,
the tracer can track you from far away.
In a field this size, it'd
take forever to find it.
Great.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
Come on, let's go. Okay.
Give me your hand I want
to lift those arms I want to
make my hands I want you to
I want you to I want you to
Let's go.
I don't think you can hear what the end.
I'm not hearty,
I'm not hearty.
I'm not hearty, I'm hearty.
I'm hearty, I'm hearty.
I'm hearty.
Next time, the Lugru Corridor.